serviio.org 2019-06-21

# Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy 

This privacy policy sets out how Six Lines Ltd. uses and protects any information that you give Six Lines Ltd. when you use this website, Alexa skill or its software.

Six Lines Ltd. is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website or its software, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Six Lines Ltd. may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 28 October 2017.

## What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * public IP address of the machine the software is running on, when using the Pro edition of the software
  * anonymous analytics on how users interact with the Alexa skill

## What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: 

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Business Transfers

If Six Lines Ltd., or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Six Lines Ltd. goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of elsten software limited may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.
